Someone is stealing Wu Shan's body.
They're even stealing Wu Shan's body.
This person must be the mastermind.
Stop right there.
Running right after eating.
What kind of magical artifact is this?
The Xuantian Soul-Scattering Bell.
It's worth a hundred taels of gold.
It is one of the three treasures of Longhu Mountain.
What are you doing?
Daoist Master,
your trick of summoning souls to deceive people is quite good.
Summoning souls for salvation is definitely not a trick.
I wonder if you, Daoist Master,
could teach me
this trick.
The secret lies in the candles.
The candles here
are all mixed with a special hallucinogenic incense.
As soon as it burns to the part with the incense,
the flame turns green.
Once inhaled, it causes hallucinations.
That's how these ghosts came about.
But as soon as the bell is rung,
these ghosts will disappear.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Did you learn it?
Where are you going?
To uncover the truth.
Want to come?
Are you Lady Hong?
Are you a human or a ghost?
I am a human.
No.
I am a ghost.
Maybe not either.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Lin Hongyuan,
the one you call
Lady Hong.
What are you doing?
Aren't you not afraid of ghosts?
Shut up.
I assume you have already heard the story
about me and that heartless man.
Now let me tell you the story
about me and Lao San.
Chen.
Let's embroider the poem you wrote yesterday
into a pair of Xuanji charts.
Alright.
I was thinking the same thing.
Then we will have to trouble you, sir,
to embroider a pair of Xuanji charts for us.
What do you say,
Chen?
Let's never part.
Get out!
If you don't leave,
my future will be ruined.
Sheng.
I'm not leaving.
Chen Sheng,
you're not that kind of person.
Chen Sheng!
You didn't die.
You survived.
Yes.
I survived.
I was saved by Lao San,
and
I lost my memory.
Who are you?
Who am I?
Wifey.
I am your wife.
Looking back at that time,
it was perhaps the best days of my life.
He raised silkworms,
and I supported the family.
Sometimes I think
it's quite nice to have no memory.
You can't remember the good,
nor the bad.
Come back early.
In heaven, may we be birds flying as one.
Hanging this love knot,
I pray to heaven
that we are united in heart for three lifetimes.
Good times don't last.
The love knot I hung on the intertwined branches
became the disaster
that shattered the beauty.
I'm fine.
The love knot under the intertwined branches
left me in a daze all day long.
But I didn't fully regain my memory.
Until one day,
I met him.
All right.
Chen,
let's never be apart.